speedsociety.com 2017-11-26

# Privacy Policy – Speed Society

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.speedsociety.com and Speed Society LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Speed Society LLC include www.speedsociety.com and Speed Society. The Speed Society website is a News and Information site. By using the Speed Society website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

#### Collection of your Personal Information

Speed Society may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Speed Society’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. Speed Society may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender and race. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Speed Society. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Speed Society website.

Speed Society encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Speed Society so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Speed Society is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Speed Society website.

#### Use of your Personal Information

Speed Society collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Speed Society may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Speed Society and its affiliates. Speed Society may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Speed Society does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Speed Society may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Speed Society may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Speed Society, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Speed Society will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Speed Society or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Speed Society; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Speed Society, or the public.

#### Use of Cookies

The Speed Society website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Speed Society pages, or register with Speed Society site or services, a cookie helps Speed Society to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Speed Society website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Speed Society features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Speed Society services or websites you visit.

#### Security of your Personal Information

To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, Speed Society uses the following:

  * Cloudflare

#### Children Under Thirteen

Speed Society does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

#### Disconnecting your Speed Society Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your Speed Society account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR SPEED SOCIETY ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may learn how to disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting their “My Account” page. Users may also contact us via email or telephone..

#### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Speed Society by contacting us here:

**Web page** : www.speedsociety.com  
**Email** : [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
**Phone** : (855) 271-1679

#### Changes to this Statement

Speed Society will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Speed Society encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Speed Society is protecting your information.

#### Contact Information

Speed Society welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Speed Society has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Speed Society at:

Speed Society, Inc.  
4122 Sorrento Valley Blvd.  
Suite 104  
San Diego, California 92121

**Email** : [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
**Phone** : (855) 271-1679

_Effective as of Jan 01, 2012_
